

Yoel De Sanctis Clemente

Address: Cartagena / Murcia Telephone: 610 81 79 73

Email: yoeldsc@gmail.com - me@yoeldsc.es

Birthdate: 13th November 1991

More information at: yoeldsc.es

About me

Hello, I am Yoel. I work as Fullstack Developer at consulting, although I focus on Frontend development and also do project management and analysis tasks.

I have a Telecomunications Engineering Degree by the Technical University of Cartagena. Additionally, I have participated actively on other projects as the Teleco LAN Party as coordinator, taking on audiovisual communication, digital marketing, web development and graphic design tasks. I have also worked at the University's Digital Content Production Centre, at web design and development projects as well as web applications focused on gamification applied to teaching.

Professional experience

2018 - Present

Frontend / Fullstack Developer

(1 year and 5 months)

Centers Developer. Everis

I have participated on automotive industry related projects, developing web applications as a fullstack developer, using mainly the Angular and Spring frameworks. I also conduct team management, analysis and estimation tasks.

2015- 2018

R&D Scholarship

(3 years and 8 months)

Digital Content Production Centre (UPCT)

I performed audiovisual production tasks as well as web applications design and development on gamification related projects.

Education

BSc. in Telematics Engineering Technical University of Cartagena (UPCT)

Final Degree Project - Lean methodologies for videogames development 2nd place at best Web application and Services Degree Project by Odilo. 2016/17

Other courses

2017

Entrepreneurship specialization

Banco Santander Yuzz - UPCT

2016

Digital Marketing course

Google Activate - UPCT

Abilities

Personal Skills

Creativity - Teamwork - Problem resolution Oral presentation - Versatile - Proactivity

Languages

Spanish (Native) - English B2 Level (FCE) - Arab A1 (EOI Cartagena)

Other Knowledge

- Agile / Lean Startup
- Analysis and Estimation
- UX
- Online Marketing
- Graphic design

- Audiovisual Production
- Gamification
- Basic notions on videogame design and development

Technical knowledge

HTML5 / CSS3 / Sass (>3 years)

JS / Typescript (2 years)

Angular 4+(2 years)

React (Basic knowledge)

Java / Spring Framework (1 year)

Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator,

Premiere, After Effects, Audition...)

Version Control / GIT

SQL

Wordpress

Jasmine / Karma (Basic knowledge)

Python (Basic knowledge)

Unreal Engine 4

Additional data

Teleco LAN Party

Annual organised event in Cartagena. Board member of the Cartagena Telematics Youth Association, as Communication coordinator from 2013 to 2019.

Other Graphic design and web development projects

From 2015 to 2018, I carried out diverse Graphic and Logo designs for various local and regional businesses, as well as web development projects using Wordpress.

FILMCAMP · La Base Escuela de Cine del Mediterráneo (Film School)

Course in which each student produced, scripted and filmed his own short. I also took a Film Photography Course.

Free Time Monitor

Maraqua, Free time education School. Scouter from 2010 to 2016 at Scout San Ginés (Cartagena).

Voluntary work at Alia2 Fundation and UPCT.

From 2013 to 2015, speaker and organizer of various Internet and new technologies security awareness for underages activities and talks.

More information at: yoeldsc.es